OK, we're in the process now where Tiffany's hair is actually starting to lighten.
If you can do a mental picture of what a hair color chart would look like, where we started her hair color was somewhere in the golden tones.
We want to get her to a little bit of a blonder stage so you actually have to lighten through these stages of color until you get to the blond where you want to be.
The biggest mistake people make is, they see this orange and they rinse it off.
You need to process through that color.
Get all the way, you want, we're working toward the blondest, to a blonder shade so don't stop at the orange stage.
How you would do that is, you want to check.
We can actually see the hair lightening and it works from where we processed it first, the very underneath.
I'm going to clip some hair out of the way so I can show you what I'm talking about and we're going to see this section of hair where it's actually lightened.
You want to take a color, excuse me, a water bottle and you, we're going to clean this off and I'll show you how this is lightened on this section of hair.